couponmom.com 2019-05-02

# Coupons, Grocery Coupons, The Coupon Mom

**Our Commitment to Privacy**  
Couponmom.com is committed to protecting your personal privacy. We provide this notice to explain the type of information we collect on the **couponmom.com** website and how we use this information. This Policy also explains the choices that you can make about the way your information is collected and used. Our Privacy Policy is available for you to review on our homepage and on every page where we have requested personally identifiable information. 

**The Information We Collect:**  
We collect email address so that you can register to receive our email newsletter. All other sponsor links have their own privacy policy which you can review on their sites. Your sponsor link participation is voluntary and they are provided to give you additional savings opportunities, but are not required to save with the Coupon Mom system.

**The Way We Use Information**

Couponmom.com only uses your information to be able to send email newsletters.  Subscribers can cancel their email subscription at any time by using the "unsubscribe" link at the bottom of the email.  We do not sell or share subscriber information with any other party.

In addition to using cookies and related technologies as described above, we also may permit certain third party companies to help us tailor advertising that we think may be of interest to users and to collect and use other data about user activities on our Sites and/or Services (e.g., to allow them to tailor ads on third party services). These companies may deliver ads that might also place cookies and otherwise track user behavior.

**Links to Other Sites**  
Users should be aware that when you are on this website you could be directed to other sites that take you outside our service. This includes links from advertisers, sponsors, and partners that have been given permission to use the Coupon Mom logo. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, or otherwise collect data or solicit personal information. Check the linked site to locate its Privacy Policy, which may be different from our own. If the Couponmom.com website links you to any third party website, Couponmom.com makes no representation as to the existence, sufficiency, accuracy or completeness of their Privacy Policy which can change at any time. 

**Our Commitment to Data Security:**  
We take reasonable precautions to keep your personal information secure. We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard the information we collect. We cannot guarantee the security of any information you disclose online, and you do so at your own risk. 

**Changes in Our Policy**  
We reserve the right to change or remove this Privacy Policy at our discretion. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy we will post those changes here. We encourage you to visit this area frequently to stay informed.   

In addition to using cookies and related technologies as described above, we also may permit certain third party companies to help us tailor advertising that we think may be of interest to users and to collect and use other data about user activities on our Sites and/or Services (e.g., to allow them to tailor ads on third party services). These companies may deliver ads that might also place cookies and otherwise track user behavior. 

**Your Consent To This Privacy Policy**  
By using this website, you signify your assent to the Couponmom.com Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with any term in this Policy, please do not use this site or submit any personally identifiable information. 

**How to Contact Us**  
Should you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy or the collection of information, please e-mail us at: [Contact Coupon Mom](https://www.couponmom.com/contact-us-12).   

Copyright © 2019 CouponMom.com - Find All The Latest Printable Coupons & Special Offers Online
